Guide to the Fales Family Papers MSS.029
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II: DeCoursey Fales
  - Subseries II.A: Correspondence
    - Fay school list, 1903-04., 1903-1904 (Box 4, Folder 184)
    - Invitations., undated (Box 4, Folder 185)
    - Journal, 1911. (Box 4, Folder 186)
    - Receipts, 1913-15., 1913-1915 (Box 4, Folder 187)
    - Poems., undated (Box 4, Folder 188)
    - Printed materials., undated (Box 4, Folder 189)
    - Scrapbook containing sympathy notes re: fathers death, 1929. (Box 4, Folder 190)
    - Scrapbook containing sympathy notes re: fathers death, 1929. (Box 4, Folder 191)
    - Scrapbook, letters of congratulations, 1941. (Box 4, Folder 192)
    - Scrapbook, letters of congratulations, 1941. (Box 4, Folder 193)
    - Scrapbook, letters of congratulations, 1941. (Box 4, Folder 194)
    - Scrapbook, letters of congratulations, 1956. (Box 4, Folder 195)
    - Photographs., undated (Box 4, Folder 196)
  - Subseries II.B: Clubs and Hobbies
    Contains half a box of documentation of the various clubs and hobbies Fales participated in, such as yacht log books, New York Flight Club meeting minutes, Harvard Club, and Masonic Lodge.
    - Alice and Nina log book, 1931. (Box 4, Folder 197)
    - Certificate to Masonic Lodge, 1922. (oversize box) (Box 4, Folder 198)
    - DeCoursey Fales, re: clubs., undated (Box 4, Folder 199)
    - Halycon log, 1911. (Box 4, Folder 200)
    - Halycon log, 1912. (Box 4, Folder 201)
    - Halycon log, 1913. (Box 4, Folder 202)
    - Halycon log, 1915. (Box 5, Folder 203)
    - Harvard Club, 1911-16., 1911-1916 (Box 5, Folder 204)
    - Notes., undated (Box 5, Folder 205)
    - Navigation workbook., undated (Box 5, Folder 206)
    - Navigation workbook., undated (Box 5, Folder 207)
    - New York Flight Club, minutes[1913], autographed copy. (Box 5, Folder 208)
    - New York Flight Club, correspondence, 1913-14., 1913-1914 (Box 5, Folder 209)
    - New York Yacht Club, 1953. (Box 5, Folder 210)
    - New York Yacht Club, memo, 1963. (Box 5, Folder 211)
    - Union Club, memo., undated (Box 5, Folder 212)
    - Value of Sailing at USNA., undated (Box 5, Folder 213)
    - Yachting magazines., undated (Box 5, Folder 214)
  - Subseries II.C: The Fales Family of Bristol, Rhode Island Book Material
    Contains half a box of items relating to the book The Fales Family of Bristol Rhode Island, including correspondence, engravings, and the Dedham Fales family ancestry of Haliburton Fales 2nd.
    - Americana Illustrated. 8. 3 (1919) (Box 5, Folder 215)
    - Eaton, A. H., correspondence from Dr. Georges Fales Baker, 1919. (Box 5, Folder 216)
    - Eaton, A. H., correspondence from genealogy societies., undated (Box 5, Folder 217)
    - Eaton, A. H., correspondence., undated (Box 5, Folder 218)
    - Eaton, A. H., correspondence to Haliburton Fales Jr., 1918. (Box 5, Folder 219)
    - Fales, DeCoursey, correspondence from A. H. Eaton, 1918. (Box 5, Folder 220)
    - Fales, DeCoursey, correspondence from A. H. Eaton, 1919. (Box 5, Folder 221)
    - Fales, DeCoursey, correspondence from Lena Evans, 1919. (Box 5, Folder 222)
    - Fales, DeCoursey, correspondence from Lena Evans, 1919. (Box 5, Folder 223)
    - Fales, DeCoursey, correspondence., undated (Box 5, Folder 224)
    - Fales, DeCoursey, correspondence from Suffolk Engraving Co., 1919. (Box 5, Folder 225)
    - Fales, DeCoursey, Dedham Fales Family Ancestry of Haliburton Fales., undated (Box 5, Folder 226)
    - Fales Family, record of deed, book 4. (handwritten by DeCoursey Fales), undated (Box 5, Folder 227)
    - Fales Family of Bristol, drawing of the house of Nehemiah and David Fales., undated (Box 5, Folder 228)
    - Fales Family of Bristol, engravings., undated (Box 5, Folder 229)
    - Fales Family of Bristol, galleys. (galley cabinet), undated (Box 5, Folder 230)
    - Fales Family of Bristol, notes., undated (Box 5, Folder 231)
    - Fales Family of Bristol, photos., undated (Box 5, Folder 232)
  - Subseries II.D: Fales Library
    Contains half a box of items relating to Fales collecting books and the NYU collection. Material includes lecture notes, Fales collection register, and pamphlets produced by NYU about the collection.
    - Egerer, J. W., DeCoursey Fales 1888-1966, July 14, 1966. (Box 5, Folder 233)
    - Fales Collection, register: 1961-1965. (Box 5, Folder 234)
    - Fales, DeCoursey, correspondence re: book collecting., undated (Box 5, Folder 235)
    - Fales, DeCoursey, lecture to Ladies of Montclair, 1960. (Box 5, Folder 236)
    - Fales, DeCoursey, lecture to NYU Fales Collection, 1960. (Box 5, Folder 237)
    - NYU, Recent Acquisitions, 1969. (pamphlet) (Box 5, Folder 238)
    - Report of the Librarian of Yale University, 1919-20., 1919-1920 (Box 5, Folder 239)
    - Winterich, John T., Fales Collection, (bound)., undated (Box 5, Folder 240)
    - Winterich, John T., The Fales Collection, 1959. (pamphlet) (Box 5, Folder 241)
    - Winterich, John T., The Fales Collection: a record growth, 1963. (pamphlet) (Box 5, Folder 242)
- Series III: DeCoursey and Haliburton Fales Library List
  - Akerly, Lucy D. Address. Annual meeting of the order of Colonial Lords of Manors in America. New York, 9 Dec. 1916. (Box 6, Folder data_value_missing_cfc1d240e1afa7380e4482d80582d8db)
  - Bell, Helen G. Winning the King's Cup. New York: G. P. Putnam's Sons, 1928. (Box 6, Folder data_value_missing_1b64660a7cd15054c775048faabf689e)
  - Bair, Frederick H., Elma A. Neal and Vernon T. Sanders. Knowing Your Language. N. p.: Macmillan Co., 1941. (Box 6, Folder data_value_missing_ad69c0ebc2a6d1f5d0cd3bb18a925cdc)
  - Brooks, Elbridge S. A Boy of the First Empire. New York: The Century Co., 1895. (Box 6, Folder data_value_missing_8c43168848cd7c2c2850cfbf5aa515f1)
  - Chancellor, Sir Christopher. Speech. Pilgrims Dinner in honor of Mr. Alistair Cooke. London, 23 Nov. 1964. (Box 6, Folder data_value_missing_5d2587163ce2f4db674895a643a7f4e2)
  - A Chapter in the History of the Queen's Cup Won by the yacht "America"in 1851. New York: George F. Nesbitt & Co., 1885. (Box 6, Folder data_value_missing_e1c7b292687d4842127badc4dc23ad93)
  - Club House of the Brook. New York: n. p., 1927. (Box 6, Folder data_value_missing_4a4aade017e67228743dd51acfb2caa0)
  - A Collection of Psalms and Hymns for the Christian Worship. Boston: Carter and Hendee, 1830. (Box 6, Folder data_value_missing_1a4689ffa0c33ec08b920a7f5d73fe0a)
  - The Cruising Club of America Year Book. N. p.: Yearbook Committee, 1949. (Box 6, Folder data_value_missing_78ba04e4778f9d0de6e4fdee69744925)
  - Dicken, Charles. A Christmas Carol Boston: Alantic Monthly Press, 1920. (Box 6, Folder data_value_missing_3a4b4de53728d080f37f8b367f96301c)
  - Drury, Samuel S. Fathers and Sons. New York: Richard R. Smith, Inc., 1930. (Box 6, Folder data_value_missing_e4e4696ba99756087a523371c542abbb)
  - Erskine, Sir David. Annals and Antiquities of Dryburgh. Kelso: Alex Leadbetter, 1836 (Box 6, Folder data_value_missing_e08ce617b2076b20cba053e27e632664)
  - Fales, De Coursey. The Fales Family of Bristol, Rhode Island. Boston: Privately printed, 1919 (Box 6, Folder data_value_missing_a773b6e057aed9870c19f0406131cd46)
  - Fales, De Coursey. The Fales Family of Bristol, Rhode Island. Boston: Privately printed, 1919 (Box 7, Folder data_value_missing_7fb8e22e6b5b86a2ca329cb971e2e4a3)
  - Fales, De Coursey. The Fales Family of Briston, Rhode Island/- extra illustrated copy. Boston: Privately printed, 1919. (Box 7, Folder data_value_missing_2f5fdac779d7a4bf6139a79ef5fbcfd7)
  - Fowler, Arture. The Ballad of Myra Gray. New York: Privately printed, 1927. (Box 7, Folder data_value_missing_809d9736957988dcdc17ce6055094cdb)
  - Freneau, Philip. Poems Vol. 2. Philadelphia: Lydia R. Bailey, 1809. (Box 7, Folder data_value_missing_9110cbcfc5d3fa2dd35048ac4e2b8f6f)
  - Goodrich, S. G. A Pictorial History of the United States. Philadelphia: E. H. Butler & Co., undated (Box 7, Folder data_value_missing_7eafb241444c81cb3f6574a227d20b33)
  - Gordan, John D. An Anniversary Exhibition. New York: New York Public Library, 1965 1860 (Box 7, Folder data_value_missing_af79bf7aa5ec5bbc79c5c0ca0511ede0)
  - Governor William Bradford's Letter Box reprint The... Mayflower Descendant. 1906. (Box 7, Folder data_value_missing_ca36559ef18fde6a39528734c4fa17d3)
  - Grandet, Eugenie. Scenes de la Vie de Province. Paris: Ancienne Maison Michel Levy Freres, 1881. (Box 7, Folder data_value_missing_61256736980bfc22a115e917a166017b)
  - Green, J. R. A Short History of the English People. London: Macmillan and Co., 1875. (Box 7, Folder data_value_missing_6d7826d792640397322b8d78e6368d7f)
  - Haliburtion, Thomas Chandler. The Clockmaker: Or, the Sayings and Doings of Samuel Slick, of Slickville. Halifax, N. S.: Joseph Howe, 1836. (Box 7, Folder data_value_missing_e82a607e046c0a1c71475322de8f43f7)
  - Hamerton, Philip Gilbert. The Life of J. M. W. Turner, R. A.. Boston: Roberts Brothers, 1879. (Box 7, Folder data_value_missing_069b6f0c6d19344a19d57e8f264ce9d2)
  - Hare, Augustus and St. Clair Baddely. Days Near Rome. London: Kegan Paul, Trench, Trubner & Co,. Ltd., 1907. (Box 7, Folder data_value_missing_966b7a5a34bab9089912e1845b2ee9ff)
  - Hart, Joseph C. The Romance of Yachting: Voyage the First. New York: Harper & Brothers, 1848 (Box 8, Folder data_value_missing_f64ad7d16a058528606ecf8043473797)
  - Hauff, Wilhelm. The Little Glass Man and Other Stories. New York: Macmillan & Co., 1894. (Box 8, Folder data_value_missing_c6366773a21ebe1b88984f0b09cdbcaa)
  - Hillquit, Morris. Socialism in Theory and Practice. New York: Macmillan Co., 1912. (Box 8, Folder data_value_missing_6b991be68af48559b9030d6111d0e9c6)
  - The Holy Bible. Oxford: Samuel Collingwood and Co., 1833. (Box 8, Folder data_value_missing_b093f0d323ea33f66a010dd1f6bf8a8a)
  - The Holy Bible. New York: American Bible Society, 1846. (Box 8, Folder data_value_missing_1b3e30791af2c7c23a94f881f2ed7a6c)
  - The Holy Bible. New York: American Bible Society, 1866. (Box 8, Folder data_value_missing_68754fe648da1c53bf3031f60b6156a3)
  - Hough, George A. Disaster on Devil's Bridge. New Bedford: The Marine Historical Association, Inc., 1963. (Box 8, Folder data_value_missing_4b1827561073bd1b957e6e0872669df6)
  - Hoyt, Deristhe L. The World's Painters and Their Pictures. Boston: Ginn & Co., 1898. (Box 8, Folder data_value_missing_be96178107efe2ad3c86969d3bc5c2e4)
  - Lehmann, R. C. Rowing London: A. D. Innes & Co., 1898. (Box 9, Folder data_value_missing_b9545f865b654fbda6ecc254ecfc37bf)
  - Lewis, Isaac Newton. Addresses on Sir Robert Walpole and Rev. Phillips Payson. Walpole, MA: First Historical Society of Walpole, 1905. (Box 9, Folder data_value_missing_5dfa9c8eadf03f0be96e517a1a1f9ee7)
  - Lippmann, Walter. A Preface to Politics. New York: Mitchell Kennerley, 1913. (Box 9, Folder data_value_missing_55cd0dcca4209ca6dc60a7fc4b443652)
  - A Liturgy for the Use of the Church at King's Chapel in Boston. Boston: Christian Examiner, 1828. (Box 9, Folder data_value_missing_6f5ea8fb19b7f7a8d368593b27b5944e)
  - Maloney, Richard C. Fifty Notable Ship Portraits at Mystic Seaport. Mystic, CT: The Marine Historical Association, Inc., 1963. (Box 9, Folder data_value_missing_e7e8b5d74ad69e9626286b7a1cb1811a)
  - Maximes du Duc de la Rochefoucauld. Paris: Librairie de Firmin, 1878. (Box 9, Folder data_value_missing_ce025a438b53ad1b7ed6a5e14668e9bb)
  - The... Mayflower Descendant. 3. 1 (1901) (Box 9, Folder data_value_missing_425a8cd22a390886d826c3576e81851b)
  - The... Mayflower Descendant. 4. 1-4 (1902) (Box 9, Folder data_value_missing_0a1072a4ca1488f82a645af62e51fec2)
  - The... Mayflower Descendant. 19. 4 (1917) (Box 9, Folder data_value_missing_815cd911a735bf163851610bef446a7f)
  - The... Mayflower Descendant. 20. 3 (1918) (Box 9, Folder data_value_missing_897bebb3c28fa64ac439076abdbfb229)
  - Memoirs of William R. Fales, the Portsmouth Cripple. Philadelphia: Lindsay & Blakiston, 1851. (Box 9, Folder data_value_missing_42043e9474ee7459ef092ebb0604e3db)
  - Meredith, George. The Egoist. New York: Charles Scribner's Sons, 1914. (Box 9, Folder data_value_missing_12870fbb4429f02d317d614c02e76a27)
  - Meredith, George. The Ordeal of Richard Feverel. New York: Charles Scribner's Sons, 1911. (Box 9, Folder data_value_missing_443c7f3b7d39e64d75b2ffefe7eb1691)
  - Messervy, George P. The Quick-Step of an Emperor: Maximilian of Mexico. London: Grant Richards Ltd., 1921. (Box 9, Folder data_value_missing_0324fbb4826fc223de1e400ef04f5741)
  - Modern British Authors. New York: Greenberg, 1930. (Box 9, Folder data_value_missing_7abe269c67a14cb642d2cbd33e23c22b)
  - Moss, George H. Nauvoo to the Hook. Locust, N. J.: Jervey Close Press, 1964. (Box 9, Folder data_value_missing_41d370dd8856701256e369e55152f72e)
  - Murray, Spencer. Cruising the Sea of Cortez. Palm Desert, CA.: Desert-Southwest, Inc. 1963 (Box 9, Folder data_value_missing_3c4926c598ee9869c371f47ef1477c18)
  - The Mythology of Greece and Rome. New York: American Book Company, n. d., undated (Box 10, Folder data_value_missing_9e9a1c24caaac9bed5444b50a39e642c)
  - The New England Historical and Genealogical Register. 2. 3 (1848) (Box 10, Folder data_value_missing_777a60d4fae8fb94f04b4add326af209)
  - The New England Historical and Genealogical Register. 71. 281 (1917) (Box 10, Folder data_value_missing_75f88255742b91139f0786acd18434c6)
  - The New England Historical and Genealogical Register. 73. 289 (1919) (Box 10, Folder data_value_missing_0ae453431804a56ab9f636ae171667f5)
  - The New York Genealogical and Biographical Record. 1. 1 (1919) (Box 10, Folder data_value_missing_7a62d0f05349b31e87ee4aadc0c6a546)
  - New York Yacht Club Yearbook. New York: n. p., 1940. (Box 10, Folder data_value_missing_19a99d86c4b1dd73fad0c599e2a7b949)
  - Nichols, Major George Ward. The Story of the Great March New York: Harper & Brothers, 1865. (Box 10, Folder data_value_missing_3a50d63111e625de934b5fa1be340c81)
  - Ogilvy, C. Stanley. Successful Yacht Racing. New York: W. W. Norton & Co., 1951. (Box 10, Folder data_value_missing_3f355aa727e58be0fca6dc252558b2c7)
  - Parkinson, John Jr. Nowhere is Too Far New York: The Cruising Club of America, Inc., 1960 (Box 10, Folder data_value_missing_b1a1ebb85cf33396663b43fb915509f1)
  - Racing at Sea Princeton: D. Van Nostrand Company, Inc., 1959. (Box 10, Folder data_value_missing_5f5e1633477cad1f3500ebc9b015894a)
  - Reid, Capt. Mayne. The Castaways: A Story of Adventure in the Wilds of Borneo. London: T. Nelson and Sons, 1870. (Box 10, Folder data_value_missing_84b6baeb611a663c9a29a50d36be17a2)
  - Robertson, R. B. Of Whales and Men New York: Alfred A. Knopf, 1954. (Box 10, Folder data_value_missing_f2bca1455134d4b0cb9b9fafc1f8c694)
  - Rogers, Rev. Charles. Genealogical Memoirs of the Family of Sir Walter Scott, Bart of Abbotsford. Edinburgh: William Paterson, 1877. (Box 10, Folder data_value_missing_485aa0fc373f8e46bb25948adc497f5f)
  - The Saint Paul's School Record. Concord, NH: Ira C. Evans Co., 1907. (Box 10, Folder data_value_missing_ce29d6222511cf71736f1e8d3b82d5a0)
  - Sawtell, Clement Cleveland. The Ship Ann Alexander of New Bedford 1805-1851. Mystic,CT: The Marine Historical Association, Inc., 1962. (Box 10, Folder data_value_missing_7fd9d0a1908cbab96b5fc397b3d40c3e)
  - Seignobos, Charles. A Political History of Europe. Trans. S. M. MacVane. New York: Henry Holt and Co., 1907. (Box 11, Folder data_value_missing_9493b446607ee151ec70335194637b6c)
  - Snyder, William and Irving O. Palmer. One Thousand Problems in Physics. Boston: Gin & Co., 1900. (Box 11, Folder data_value_missing_09aec69d6116bea2159151c8808cba26)
  - Some Historical Notes on the Early Days of the Bank for Savings in the City of New York. New York: n. p., 1944. (Box 11, Folder data_value_missing_af20062c0bfacee3d84ee2620c3c0b12)
  - Southerland, B. D. L. The Arithmetical Table Book. New York: Daniel Slote & Co., 1873. (Box 11, Folder data_value_missing_a64eb6e0752ca37c61ea2d5ceeeb24d3)
  - Stackpole, Edouard A. Figureheads & Ship Carvings at Mystic Seaport. Mystic, CT: The Marine Association, Inc., 1964. (Box 11, Folder data_value_missing_0cc4285303a2f979975ae0176af434a3)
  - Taft, Henry W. Kindred Arts. New York: The Macmillan Company, 1929. (Box 11, Folder data_value_missing_84b92e2866cd0f7b6fa0f5d54cfd2274)
  - Those in Peril on the Sea. New York: The Dial Press, 1962. (Box 11, Folder data_value_missing_f98e02c37703537a20cea69af8a38705)
  - Thurber, Frederick. The Memoirs of an Ancient Mariner. Providence, RI: n. p, 1965. (Box 11, Folder data_value_missing_a6712c06d5b8b31bb4558364ff4de65b)
  - Turgenev, Ivan. Rudin. Trans. Constance Garnett. New York: Macmillan & Co., 1894. (Box 11, Folder data_value_missing_175b9b5f8b1950edb598d3760b4e143f)
  - Turgenev, Ivan. Virgin Soil. Trans. T. S. Perry. New York: Henry Holt and Company, 1877. (Box 11, Folder data_value_missing_f8183b25f65635e688f5317109c664f1)
  - United States Naval Institute Proceedings. 87. 7 (1961) (Box 11, Folder data_value_missing_a05a3232867cfb2e55061499c03ab9fb)
  - U. S. S. Seattle, During the War. Brooklyn: n. p., 1919. (Box 11, Folder data_value_missing_13b5c6c42f4a47ed68aeabb7975f36c7)
  - Willis, N. Parker. Trenton Falls. New York: George P. Putnam, 1851. (Box 11, Folder data_value_missing_1f7a8543e673eb566459916994b8f16e)
  - Wilson, James Grant. The Life and Letters of Fitz-Greene Halleck. New York: D. Appleton and Company, 1869. (Box 11, Folder data_value_missing_96d109ba7684feef7e5f58a7b07fecb9)
  - Yachting in North America. New York: D. Van Nostrand Company, Inc., 1948. (Box 11, Folder data_value_missing_cf891a6521b98a370dad8fa4944df3c3)
- Series IV: DeCoursey Fales Auction Catalogs
  - American Art Association 1913-1929 (Box 12, Folder data_value_missing_d0787889a5bb2361e593982317c73519)
  - John Anderson Jr. 1900 (Box 12, Folder data_value_missing_9e85743f655cfff29894f4164d3f429c)
  - John Anderson Jr. 1901-1903 (Box 13, Folder data_value_missing_bbe764b7000c9eab94ebbaa3bf658337)
  - Anderson Auctions Co. 1904-1913 (Box 13, Folder data_value_missing_29a4d4bc4693da8d1d78b44529203d05)
  - Metropolitan Arts Assn. 1914 (Box 13, Folder data_value_missing_17d2ce3ed3cfeb6e34ba3e42e1ac86fc)
  - Anderson Galleries 1916-1918 (Box 13, Folder data_value_missing_15aaf57e5bc88852b9b07fa49f980785)
  - Anderson Galleries 1918-1928 (Box 14, Folder data_value_missing_c93991609f1ce84e649db36f34db4cb8)
  - American Art Assn. Anderson Galleries 1929-Oct. 27, 1930, 1929-1930 (Box 14, Folder data_value_missing_27e608265e3d27b0552d092c7091d7f2)
  - American Art Assn. Anderson Galleries Nov. 12, 1930-May 1934, 1930-1934 (Box 15, Folder data_value_missing_087ea052fcb042a2e5d896dd98826379)
  - American Art Assn. Anderson Galleries Oct. 25, 1934-April 16, 1936, 1934-1936 (Box 16, Folder data_value_missing_965e4d1ce26da3e922e492a8779e88cb)
  - American Art Assn. Anderson Galleries April 23, 1936-May 22, 1939, 1936-1939 (Box 17, Folder data_value_missing_013946428f8628dee57cbbcf09450513)
  - Bangs & Co. 1894-1901 (Box 17, Folder data_value_missing_bf4b2967afbfe781fa9b659f57b786dc)
  - Charles S. Boesen, undated (Box 17, Folder data_value_missing_d467e4c7435101ac926c705e7cdfcf52)
  - Charles Hamilton Auction 1966 (Box 18, Folder data_value_missing_f507497bf4ed9d7f4a68af1927b5ffb2)
  - Kende Galleries 1949-1949 (Box 18, Folder data_value_missing_01e2dd0cc553ad49530fd7e134e830a1)
  - C. F. Libbie & Co. 1938 (Box 18, Folder data_value_missing_603bafcebc755795aee5615b2f277d87)
  - Samuel Marx, Inc. 1932 (Box 18, Folder data_value_missing_1ca16d20bcabf8245c524b100d51bb09)
  - Elkin Mathews 1922-Cat. #48 (Box 18, Folder data_value_missing_43eee6edfdcc56e64a856e38bd04b064)
  - Elkin Mathews Cat. #49-#162, undated (Box 19, Folder data_value_missing_3f3a33112a59271ffdf67fd37c793ab9)
  - Elkin Mathews Cat. #165-#180, undated (Box 20, Folder data_value_missing_54f6b482f60f3a29136615f0c89b2456)
  - Merwin-Clayton Sales Co. 1905-1911 (Box 20, Folder data_value_missing_741a38ec5381f63336b187a9d11236d5)
  - National Art Galleries 1935 (Box 20, Folder data_value_missing_19dcba00490cc631b4b8c1ca2c3e6bb3)
  - Parke-Bernet Galleries 1934-Feb. 29, 1940, 1934-1940 (Box 20, Folder data_value_missing_c915acf23d32b6e028ce0e51daea7f5b)
  - Parke-Bernet Galleries May 9, 1940-Oct. 29, 1940, 1940-1940 (Box 21, Folder data_value_missing_c78f0f1802cb68e9f93c09a8325324da)
  - Parke-Bernet Galleries Nov. 5, 1942-Jan. 16, 1946, 1942-1946 (Box 22, Folder data_value_missing_d03cc25a36000a121180b8923d9e21df)
  - Parke-Bernet Galleries Feb. 12,1946-Mar. 29, 1949, 1946-1949 (Box 23, Folder data_value_missing_19cd18f5d0c5c0a43ad28e58e0b6d46b)
  - Parke-Bernet Galleries April 27, 1949-Mar. 30, 1955, 1949-1955 (Box 24, Folder data_value_missing_7df650fb7ccc6e5771ccb1163351ea05)
  - Parke-Bernet Galleries April 27, 1955-Jan. 15, 1964, 1955-1964 (Box 25, Folder data_value_missing_beedd0ec3a10e0f644aa91e0309ee2cc)
  - Parke-Bernet Galleries Jan. 29, 1964-May 12, 1964, 1964-1964 (Box 26, Folder data_value_missing_00b0253e75e936e909b5eff98e42b262)
  - Plaza Art Galleries 1937, 1939 (Box 26, Folder data_value_missing_84267cf5e76ee79b936dad58cbd1f3d1)
  - Bernard Quaritch 1930, 1935 (Box 26, Folder data_value_missing_0d4c38ff43cd5f06e3d274bb3e38fb62)
  - Ritter-Hopson Galleries 1933 (Box 26, Folder data_value_missing_d5ea9a29a982635a7ae0fd47b0823388)
  - William Robinson Ltd. 1941 (Box 26, Folder data_value_missing_762284394d0f9fba6941eb356a0a3245)
  - Sotheby & Co. 1907-1960 (Box 26, Folder data_value_missing_c36563bb734924c160611e6a34ee200f)
  - Swann Galleries Sept. 25, 1952-March 18, 1953, 1952-1953 (Box 26, Folder data_value_missing_24e6235a940f5ab504bdd9331420d14c)
  - Swann Galleries April 22, 1953-Dec. 15, 1966, 1953-1966 (Box 27, Folder data_value_missing_2a24d872e0244a899b167f2e90f1dcd3)
  - Wadpole Galleries 1919 (Box 27, Folder data_value_missing_6bcd6deadba02cad28eb9ac4bddd470b)
  - Dunlap, Andrew 1794-1835, newspaper obituaries, 1835. (Box 28 (oversize), Folder 15)
  - Dunlap, Samuel 1825-1905, certificate as Comissioner of New York State, 1949. (Box 28 (oversize), Folder 27)
  - Dunlap, Samuel 1825-1905, French Visa, 1846. (Box 28 (oversize), Folder 28)
  - Fales, Haliburton Jr. 1849-1929, Mystic Mecca Temple certificate of membership, 1909. (Box 28 (oversize), Folder 65)
  - Helman de l'Academie des Arts de Lille en Flandre, Assemble Nationale, engraving, 1790. (Box 28 (oversize), Folder 80a.)
  - Dunlap, L. A. C. A. 1805-1887, misc. legal documents. (Box 28 (oversize), Folder 92a.)
  - Fales, Elizabeth Jane(Beale) 1821-1900, misc. legal documents. (Box 28 (oversize), Folder 109)
  - Fales, Haliburton 1815-1869, legal document. (Box 28 (oversize), Folder 127)
  - Oldridge, Alethea, will, 1810. (Box 28 (oversize), Folder 161)
  - Bradford & Fales family tree., undated (Box 28 (oversize), Folder 165)
  - Haliburton family tree., undated (Box 28 (oversize), Folder 171)
  - Fales, DeCoursey 1888-1966, certificate to Masonic Lodge, 1922. (Box 28 (oversize), Folder 198)
  - Fales, DeCoursey 1888-1966, Union Club memo., 1909. (Box 28 (oversize), Folder 212)
- Accretion 2000
  Accretions 2000 is a group of documents ranging from the mid to late 1800s. The materials were sorted and many docketed by Dorothy Mildred Mitchell Fales. They were not subdived into subseries.
  - Fales, Haliburton 1815-1869, passports, 1844, 1865. (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Fales, Haliburton 1815-1869, correspondence from Augusta "Gussie" Dunlap and Susan Maria Fales (his sisters), 1846. (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Fales, Haliburton, 1815-1869, correspondence from Augusta Fales Dunlap (his sister), 1850. (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Fales, Haliburton, 1815-1869, correspondence from Samuel B. Fales (his brother), 1847. (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Fales, Haliburton, 1815-1869, correspondence from Susan Maria Fales (his sister), 1849, 1851, [undated]. (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Fales, Haliburton, 1815-1869, correspondence from Samuel Willard Bridgham, 1848. (Box 29, Folder 6)